cheddr.com 2017-09-03

# Privacy Policy - cheddr

Privacy Statement

Data privacy is important to Spiffy Technology, Inc. and its affiliates (“Spiffy Tech”). This Privacy Statement describes the personal information we collect about you as a visitor to our websites such as [www.cheddr.com](https://www.workday.com/en-us/homepage.html), or other Spiffy Tech websites that link to this Privacy Statement, how we use it, with whom we share it, and describes your choices regarding certain types of processing. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Statement, contact privacy@cheddr.com or see the “Contact Us” section later in this statement.

By visiting our websites or providing us with your personal information, you consent to the collection, processing, and storage of your personal information as described in this Privacy Statement.

Information Collected

Spiffy Tech collects, processes, and retains information about you when you visit our websites. You may choose to provide us with information, such as your name, email address, company information, street address, telephone number, or other information, to access protected information on our websites or so we can follow up with you after your visit. We may combine other publicly available information related to the organization from which you work for with the information that you provide to us. Spiffy Tech may observe your activities, interactions, preferences, transactional information, and other computer and connection information (such as IP address) relating to your use of our websites and our services. We may also use log files, cookies and similar technologies to collect information about the pages you view, links you click on, and other actions you may take when accessing our websites, services, or emails. For more information about our use of these technologies and how to control them, see our Cookies and Similar Technologies section below. We may collect and store this information and combine this information with other personal information you may have provided.

Customer Data

As part of Spiffy Tech‘s services, customers may load data into Spiffy Tech servers. Spiffy Tech will not share or distribute any such customer data except as provided in the contractual agreement between Spiffy Tech and customer, or as may be required by law. 

Use of Your Information

Spiffy Tech uses the information we collect about you to:

  * Provide you with the Spiffy Tech websites and any support you may request;
  * Respond to your inquiries or fulfill your requests;
  * Diagnose website technical problems;
  * Send you information that we believe may be of interest to you, such as product announcements, newsletters, educational materials, and upcoming events
  * Send you administrative information such as notices related to product, service, or policy changes;
  * Understand how our websites and services are being used;
  * Personalize your experience on our websites and present products or features that are tailored to your interests;
  * Prevent, detect, mitigate, and investigate fraudulent or illegal activity; and
  * As described to you when we collect the information.

Disclosure

Spiffy Tech does not share, sell, rent, or trade personal information collected through its websites with third parties for their sole promotional purposes or as otherwise outlined in this Privacy Statement. Spiffy Tech may share information with third party service providers contracted to provide services on our behalf. These third party service providers may only use information we provide to them as requested and instructed by Spiffy Tech.

Spiffy Tech may offer solely or jointly with third parties, webinars, white paper downloads, or other services related to Spiffy Tech offerings or services. We may share your contact information and product interest in these offering or services with third parties to communicate with you.

Spiffy Tech may disclose information in special cases when we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect and defend our rights or property; (c) enforce the website Terms and Conditions; or (d) act to protect the interests of our users or others.

If Spiffy Tech goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personal information collected through our website(s) may be among the assets transferred. A prominent notice will appear on our website(s) for 30 days after any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

Cookies and Similar Technologies

Cookies are small text files that our websites ask to place on your computer’s hard drive. If your browser is set to accept cookies, then your browser adds the text in a small file. We do not use cookies to read any other information on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookie technology to authenticate your access to various areas of our websites, understand your interests, help analyze web traffic, and tailor content to your preferences. You can configure your browser to refuse cookies, or to warn you before a cookie is placed. If you disable cookies, some parts of our websites may not function properly or at all.

We use web beacons or transparent GIF files, that may be included on our websites and messages, that are typically used in conjunction with cookies, to help us manage our online advertising and measure its effectiveness, identify our users, and analyze traffic. Web beacons may also assist us with understanding which advertisements are most effective by notifying us if webpages, emails, or ads have been viewed or clicked. The information that we collect by means of these technologies is anonymous.

We may also use other technologies similar to cookies and web beacons such as HTML5 Local Storage, local shared objects, tags, and scripts. These technologies are used for similar purposes as cookies and web beacons. These technologies can operate across all of your browsers, and in some instances will require additional steps beyond browser settings to manage their use and removal. We, and our third party partners use these technologies to provide certain features on our website, to display advertising based on your web browsing activities, and/or to store content information and preferences. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing these technologies.

Do Not Track

Without a common industry or legal standard for interpreting Do Not Track (DNT) signals, Spiffy Tech does not respond to browser DNT signals. We will continue to monitor further development of a DNT standard by the privacy community and industry.

Online Advertising

Some online advertising uses information collected about your web browsing behavior such as the pages you have visited or the searches you have made. This information may be used to display more relevant advertisements and content to you on the Spiffy Tech website and non-Spiffy Tech websites. This information may also be used to display Spiffy Tech employment opportunities to you if, for example, you have visited our careers page. The information collected is linked to an anonymous cookie ID (alphanumeric number); it does not include any information that could be linked back to a particular person, such as their name, address or credit card number. The information used for targeted advertising may come from Spiffy Tech or through third party ad networks.

Data Processing

Any personal information collected about EU visitors via our websites is processed in the United States by Spiffy Tech or by a third party acting on our behalf. When you provide personal information to Spiffy Tech, you consent to the processing of your information in the United States. Our websites are hosted in the United States.

Third-Party Websites

This website may contain links to other sites that Spiffy Tech does not own or control and whose privacy practices may differ from those of Spiffy Tech. Please be aware that Spiffy Tech is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our websites. We recommend that you read the privacy statement of each website that collects personal information, as their privacy statement will govern any personal information you submit to those sites. This Privacy Statement applies only to information collected by Spiffy Tech websites.

Testimonials

We may post customer testimonials on our websites that may contain personal information such as the customer’s name. We obtain the customer’s consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you wish to request the removal of your testimonial, contact us at [privacy@cheddr.com](chrome-extension://gbkeegbaiigmenfmjfclcdgdpimamgkj/views/qowt.html#mailto:privacy@cheddr.com).

Social Media Features and Widgets

Our websites may include social media features, such as YouTube videos, the Facebook Like button, and widgets such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our websites. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our websites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our websites. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing it.

Security

Spiffy Tech employs industry standard security measures to ensure the security of information. However, the security of information transmitted through the Internet can never be guaranteed. Spiffy Tech is not responsible for any interception or interruption of any communications through the Internet or for changes to or losses of information. Users of our sites are responsible for maintaining the security of any password, user ID, or other form of authentication involved in obtaining access to password protected or secure areas of any Spiffy Tech websites. In order to protect you and your information, Spiffy Tech may suspend your use of a website, without notice, pending an investigation, if any breach of security is suspected. Access to and use of password protected and/or secure area of any Spiffy Tech site is restricted to authorized users only. Unauthorized access to such areas is prohibited and may lead to criminal prosecution.

Opt-Out

If at any time after registering for information, your personal information changes or you change your mind about receiving information from us, send us a request specifying updated information or your new choice. Simply send your request to [privacy@cheddr.com](chrome-extension://gbkeegbaiigmenfmjfclcdgdpimamgkj/views/qowt.html#mailto:privacy@cheddr.com) or postal mail at the contact information listed below. Use the same email address if you do not wish to receive our newsletters, including the Spiffy Tech newsletter.

Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Statement or if you need to update, change or remove information, you can do so by contacting privacy@cheddr.com or by regular mail addressed to:

Spiffy Technology, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy  
300 Cagney Lane #105

Newport Beach, CA, US 92821  
United States

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact us via the information above. We will respond to your request to access or delete your information within 30 days. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Changes to this Privacy Statement

We reserve the right to change or update this Privacy Statement at any time. Changes to the Privacy Statement will be posted on this website and links to the Privacy Statement will indicate that the statement has been changed or updated. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Statement for any changes. For new users, changes or updates are effective upon posting. For existing users, changes or updates are effective 30 days after posting.
